'Cause we got a little ol' convoy
Rockin' through the night
Yeah, we got a little ol' convoy
Ain't she a beautiful sight
Come on and join our convoy
Ain't nothin' gonna get in our way
We gonna roll this truckin' convoy
'Cross the USA
Convoy
Breaker. This here's the Duck.
And you wanna back off of them hogs?
MAN 2:10-4. About five miles or so.
Ten, roger.
Hmm. I better check the fluid levels.
We're okay on Coke syrup.
Oh, man. Come on!
Coming through!
Okay. Yeah.
Hmm!
What's that black cracker?
A tomato.
You're not gonna eat a sandwich
from a truck-stop men's room, are you?
Eh, what's the worst thing
that could happen?
Ugh. It's like a party in my mouth,
and everyone's throwing up.
Lookie there. It's one of them things
like on our mud flaps.
Yosemite Sam?
Stands back.
I'm gonna puts my moves on her.
Whoa-oh-oh-oh-oh!
That jerk! No one hoots at my captain
unless they're prepared
to take it to the next level.
Fry, please. That's sweet,
but I'd rather not even dignify them
with an ass-whupping.
Yo, sexy mama.
Let's get busy and freaky, in that order.
Hey, jumbo! How would you
like it if Leela said you were sexy
and she wanted to make love with you?
Eh, I gots five minutes.
She looks pretty good
for a truck-stop chick.
You take that back! She does not look good
for a truck-stop chick!
Yeah, you're right. She don't gots
enough meat for a guy like me.
She does too! She's loaded with meat.
She's got more meat than a cow. Ow!
More meat than a cow!
I just can't please Leela
no matter what I do.
I just want her to like me.
Well, there's always hope.
Come on. We gotta go fix
the plasma-fusion boiler.
Who are you?
Scruffy, a janitor.
Why aren't you fixing the boiler?
Schedule conflict.
There. Fixed forever.
Scruffy's gonna die the way he lived.
Oh, marmalade!
Oh, the hypochondriac's back.
So, what is it this time?
Well, my lead pipe hurts a little.
That's normal. Next patient!
Hmm.
He's a witch!
Fry, did you eat anything
- unusual recently?
- No.
What about that bathroom egg salad
from the truck stop?
I've had better.
Egg salad? Hmm.
Zoidberg will have to examine
your gastrointestinal tract.
Come, everyone. Give Fry some privacy.
If you can't see well enough
through the two-way mirror,
there'll be a close-up
on this video screen.
Hmm.
We'll need to have a look inside you
with this camera.
Guess again.
Gross!
Go, man, go!
Watch for any subtle irregularity
in Fry's bowel.
Wow!
It's gorgeous.
That place used to be a big dump.
Wow!
Worms?
Ew! Puke-a-tronic!
So the eggs in that
egg salad sandwich were...
Correct! Worm eggs.
And the mayonnaise
was probably none too fresh either.
It's nauseating, mon!
Is there no way to get rid
of the disgusting maggots?
Only one.
We'll have to travel deep inside Fry...
in this!
- Shotgun!
In each gastro-survival kit,
you'll find a rain slicker,
a disposable fun camera,
and something to protect you
against bacteria: a harpoon.
Yo, old guy.
Why do we have to use
those tiny micro-droids?
Can't you just shrink us?
Oh, my, no.
That would require extremely tiny atoms,
and have you priced those lately?
I'm not made of money. Leave me alone!
Me next!
Oh!
Anyhoo, your net suits
will let you experience
Fry's worm-infested bowels
as if you were actually
wriggling through them.
There's no part of that sentence
I didn't like.
Is everyone present?
- We're all here.
- Definitely.
Here's the plan.
We'll enter the ear,
drip down the back of the throat,
and make for the bowel.
There, we'll irritate
the pelvic splanchnic ganglion
and cause an intestinal spasm,
expelling, among other things,
the parasites.
I'll tell Fry to wash out,
among other things, his ear.
No! Fry can't know anything
about the mission.
If he finds out,
the worms will try to defend themselves.
They know everything he knows.
They know how to make ice cream soup?
Leela, your role is to distract Fry
so he doesn't notice what we're up to.
Can do!
Leela, you should really
try a facial scrub for your pores.
- Look! A starling!
- Really?
Shh.
Be very quiet.
We're in the ear.
Okay, Professor.
- What?
- What about what?
Uh... What if we go for a walk, possibly,
because it's such a lovely day, perhaps.
I'd love to.
We gotta get someplace
where he won't stick his finger.
It's hopeless! Abandon ship!
Wait! We just have
to get past the eardrum!
What are those worms
doing to Fry's brain?
They're giving it a complete tune-up.
A cursory glance would suggest
they've doubled his thinking power.
My God! Soon he'll be smarter than Cher.
Ah. The scent of a rose.
Curious how an aromatic chain
of hydrocarbons
can evoke our deepest emotions.
For you.
That's such a beautiful thought, Fry.
And what's more amazing, you expressed it
without spewing crumbs at me.
Brace yourselves, everyone.
We're entering the interior of Fry's nose.
We're at finger alert five.
Let's just pray nothing stimulates
the delicate smell receptors.
Nobody make a smell.
Quick! We can escape
through that nasal capillary
into the sinus.
Strange.
Usually you don't know anything
about human anatomy.
I learned it from
a decongestant commercial.
Soothing action, action, action, action.
Where are we, the ass?
We're in the heart,
better known as the love muscle.
Where the food is digested.
We should be safe,
just so long as nothing
makes it beat faster.
Abandon ship!
No! Set course for that
cholesterol-encrusted valve.
It's good cholesterol,
but it spreads like bad cholesterol.
Look, they're Jazzercising
Fry's muscles.
He'll be as strong and flexible
as Gumby and Hercules combined.
Gumbercules? I love that guy.
Ugh. It's that jerk from the truck stop.
Let's cross the street
and try to blend in
with that crowd of pimps.
I don't think so.
Sir, I believe you owe this lady
an apology.
Fry, no!
He's bulging with what could be muscles.
Ooh!
I gots your apologies right heres.
Sorrys, ma'am.
I've learnsed a lesson about not
ogling cans that I won't soons forgets.
Ah, the stomach...
scenic gateway to the bowel.
Abandon ship!
No! Don't give up now.
We're but a stone's throw
from the pyloric sphincter.
We made it!
There it is,
the stately capitol of Fry's bowel.
A heavily guarded fortress surrounding
the pelvic splanchnic ganglion.
I've heard of that. Who said I haven't?
If we can stimulate that nerve,
the bowel will convulse,
expelling the entire worm society.
But what about the worms
in the other parts of his body?
Listen, this is gonna be
one hell of a bowel movement.
Afterwards, he'll be lucky
if he has any bones left.
All right. Let's smoosh some worms!
Worms to battle stations!
I had a great time today...
the flowers, the puddle,
the way you hurt that guy.
- But can I ask you something?
- Anything.
Why did you do all that stuff?
Leela, there's something
I've wanted to tell you for a long time,
but every time I try, I get nervous
and my mouth feels like it's stuffed
with peanut butter, even when it's not.
What is it? Is it about Bender?
- No, it's about you and me.
- And Bender?
Bender's not involved.
Leela, I love you.
- You do?
- Yes.
But it's only recently that I've been able
to articulate my thoughts.
I love you, Leela, and I always have.
Fry, that's the sweetest,
most wonderful... Wait.
Recently? Like since you ate
that toilet sandwich?
Yeah. I don't know why,
but my life really turned around that day.
Stay here.
Freshen your Narcotina?
Please. I need something
to settle my stomach.
The nerve is through here.
Where's Zoidberg?
Yippee-ki-yay!
You'll never guess where I've been!
One, two, three!
- Mmm.
- There it is!
The pelvic splanchnic ganglion.
Tickle it, then get ready
for the ride of your lives.
Don't even think
about tickling that ganglion.
Leela!
You're just in time to help.
If we don't get rid of the worms now,
they'll burrow so deep into the bowel
that not even Hermes' famous jerk prunes
could dislodge them.
I call it Caribbean Drano.
Fry will be stuck with the worms forever.
Perfect.
Ouch!
Oh, I'm okay.
Leela, you ignorant dope!
Now the worms will be in Fry forever.
So? Did you ever stop to think
that Fry is better off with worms?
Oh, that's stupid!
If anyone wants to tell me
what's going on here,
I'll be in the lounge.
Of all the parasites I've had
over the years,
these worms are among the...
Hell, they are the best!
Leela, how can I ever repay you
for saving them?
I'll think of something.
Hello! What's all this then?
Apartment One-I.
The old me would've made
a joke about that.
I should warn you.
It's a little under-furnished.
I'm thinking of having a window installed.
I think the view's perfect already.
Oh, that's the corniest thing
I've ever heard.
Let me show you the bedroom.
Wait. In a minute.
A holophonor?
Only a few people
in the whole universe can play that,
and they're not very good at it.
They don't have you to inspire them.
I don't have words to say
how wonderful you are, Fry.
I haven't felt this happy since
double-soup Tuesday at the orphanarium.
When I'm with you,
every day seems like double-soup Tuesday.
Oh, Fry. I love what you've become.
What I've become.
What is it?
There's just something I have to find out.
Who controls this bowel?
Who wants to know?
I am the Lord Mayor of Cologne.
You mean Colon?
State your business.
Your Excellency,
have you ever been in love?
No. I thought I was once,
but then I remembered
our species reproduces
with a cloud of spores.
Well, a wonderful girl loves me,
but I need to know
if it's really me she loves,
or just what you worms have made of me.
That's why, with all due respect,
I'm asking you to leave.
Listen, you! I was born here.
I raised a cloud of children here.
My ancestors came over here
on the sandwich.
No one can make me leave.
Everyone out of my body
or the brain gets it!
He's bluffing.
No creature would willingly
make an idiot out of itself.
Obviously you've never been in love.
Ow!
Ow! Ow!
And now, the hand-eye coordination lobe.
No! Stop that! Stop it, man!
You've damaged your brain, Universe,
but no more than a week of binge drinking
or five minutes on a cell phone.
I was just working my way
toward the medulla oblongata,
control center of the heart and lungs.
And if I kill myself, you die with me.
- No!
- Stop!
Wait a minute, man!
I hope Satan has a nice colon,
'cause that's where
you're gonna be living!
Stop! We'll leave.
But one day you'll be eating
a fast-food burger and boom!
You'll be crawling with us again.
Ever wonder what makes special sauce
so special?
Yo.
Fry! I missed you.
Did you find out
what you needed to find out?
I'm about to.
Leela, let me play for you one more time.
You don't have to do that.
I'm still seduced from before.
Please. It's important to me.
What's that supposed to mean?
I don't know.
I got nervous
and I started thinking about neck bolts.
Wow! Did you see that vase break?
It was all, like...
What's happened to you?
Nothing. I got rid of the worms.
What? Why would you do that?
Leela, I had worms.
I needed to know who you loved,
me or them.
Well, which of you wrote me that sonnet?
I did! I think.
It was probably about 50-50.
But that's how
I really felt about you, I swear.
I don't know.
Please, give me a chance
to be romantic on my own.
I've got a baggie of massage oil,
I'm gonna give you
my super back rub,
just like I used to give Amy
when I was going out with her,
and she always seemed to... Uh-oh.
Sorry you struck out, sausage link.
If it's any consolation, my life is great.
Babes, bucks, I got it all.
Well, at least I learned
Leela's a lost cause.
I give up.
There you go!
Good night.
I gotta get up early
to go parasailing with movie stars.